Aryan Awasthi

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/aryan-awasthi-b0271b1b7/

Behance profile: https://www.behance.net/aryanaw

Github: https://github.com/1999-aryan

Email aryan.16awasthi@gmail.com Mobile: +91-9169580612

F-5385 Rajajipuram, Sec-11 Lucknow, UP

#### About Me

A passionate goal-oriented individual, fond of design and development, over the years I've skilled myself with different designing tools, coding languages, and research on how to make perfect-looking designs in addition to converting them into code for development purposes. I've been into UIUX designing and development as Frontend for the past 2 years inventing my own team for social work till here ready to help organizations with design and development work, and my leadership, communication, and adaptability make them key to delivering my best growth to the organization.

## Education

### School of Management and Sciences

B-tech CSE; CGPA: 7.2

St. Joseph Montessori School

12th Standard; CGPA:6.1

City Montessori School

10th standard; CGPA:7.2

Lucknow, India

Mar 2018 - Jul 2022

Lucknow, India

Mar 2016 - Jul 2017

Lucknow, India

Mar 2014 - Jul 2015

# TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION

- User Experience Design Essentials Adobe XD UI UX Design
- Complete full stack Web Development Bootcamp
- SQL MySQL for Data Analytics and Business Intelligence
- 100 days Python Bootcamp Certification Complete Digital Marketing Certification

#### Skills Summary

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Python, MySQL
- Framework: BOOTSTRAP, React-js
- Design tool: Figma, AdobeXD, Prototyping, Wireframing, smart animation, Photoshop, Illustrator, Invision, Sketch, Framer Miro, Canva
- Extra: Leadershsip, Mentor, Advisor

## Experience

Technical mentor

Hawkdawk Remote, India

 $Product\ Designer\ intern:\ UI/UX\ designer,\ Tools:\ Figma,\ Adobe.XD,\ Canva,\ social\ media\ creator.$ 

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022

# • Densat FM Service PVT LTD

Digital Marketer Intern: Wordpress landing page design and development, Social media creator, Graphic designer, product manager. Sep 2022 - Nov 2022

#### Technical Team social Startup

Voyagers, club, Lucknow, India

Jul 2020 - Jun 2022

Voyagers, club invented: Guiding juniors/members all about UIUX web/mobile design and development.

# Real life + Academic Projects

- Trainingz4u: A WordPress site designed and developed all by me, with Elementor, designed with Figma. trainingz4u.com
- Musicionation: Skill used: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript: A music demo site developed to view and take ideas for the design so that in the future if anyone needs any design they might have a conversation for the process https://1999-aryan.github.io/passion.github.io
- Behance Projects We/Mobile designs: A portfolio setup where I add all my projects of designs, prototypes, wireframes, smart animated designs, and much more Behance link to follow "Click here".
- Tindog demo site development: A site for your pet to meet and make new friends around and have fun with being more energetic and young Tindog site view